Guide to the Martha Wilson Papers, 1950-2021 (bulk 1964-2006) MSS.175
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VIII: Objects, 1960-2005
  - folded paper labeled El Ropo Cigar Company, undated (Box 72, Object ID: 175.2.0019)
  - Plastic Knife in Box, 1985 (Box 72, Object ID: 175.2.0021)
    Box is addressed to Amei Wallach and the return address is Happy Valley Rest Home
  - Objects from envelope labeled Byars Askevold and Richards Jarden, undated (Box 72, Object ID: 175.2.0022)
    items include a matchbook with a photograph, a paper scroll and inscribed tokens with Richard Jardens and Martha Wilson's name on them.
  - Box with cards labeled Personal Oracle, undated (Box 72, Object ID:175.2.0023)
  - Box containing items from folder labeled 1988 (Box 70, Object ID: 175.2.0024)
    Objects include a fan, a rubber stamp, a box of matches, a candy box, a button with the phrase "I am a young jazz immortal" and a home pregnancy test.
  - Buttons from envelope labled activist buttons, undated (Box 70, Object ID:175.2.0025)
  - WilliWear Artist T-Shirt packaging for Jenny Holzer and Les Levine tishirts, undated (Box 70, Object ID: 175.2.0026)
  - Lapp Princess Press t-shirts in packaging, undated (Box 70, Object ID:175.2.0027)
  - Jar labelled Genuine Melinda Hair, undated (Box 70, Object ID: 175.2.0028)
  - Printed fabric with cat picture and Martha Wilson's name., 1976 (Box 70, Object ID:175.2.0029)
  - Aussie Kangaroo Pouch genuine kangaroo scrotum, undated (Box 72, Object ID:175.2.0030)
  - McCall's Magazine Advent Calendar, undated (Box 72, Object ID: 175.2.0031)
  - Red Bag of Rice, undated (Box 99, Object ID: 175.2.0032)
  - Bag containing article, fork, pencil, and eraser, undated (Box 99, Object ID: 175.2.0033)
  - Folder Labeled My Watercolor Folder and Happy Mothers Day, Comley, undated (Box 71, Object ID:175.2.0034)
  - Fan labeled a.k.a FAN CLUB, undated (Box 71, Object ID: 175.2.0035)
  - Paper Crown, undated (Box 71, Object ID: 175.2.0036)
  - Windup Gorilla Keychain, undated (Box 99, Object ID: 175.2.0037)
  - Reverend Billy and the Church of Stop Shopping Fans, 2005 (Box 71, Object ID: 175.2.0038)
  - Comley's 2002 Duke Calender (Box 71, Object ID: 175.2.0039)
  - Paper Hat, undated (Box 71, Object ID: 175.2.0040)
  - Paper Hat labeled Iron Man Award Comly, undated (Box 71, Object ID: 175.2.0041)
  - Eileen Fisher 2003 Calendar (Box 71, Object ID: 175.2.0049)
  - Receipt paper in envelope labeled 7/31/03 from Ricardo Miranda Zuniga (Box 71, Object ID: 175.2.0042)
  - Small gold sword, undated (Box 99, Object ID:175.2.0043)
  - Misc buttons, undated (Box 99, Object ID: 175.2.0044)
  - CBGB wristband, undated (Box 71, Object ID:175.2.0045)
  - Small tile with the letter M, undated (Box 99, Object ID: 175.2.0046)
  - paper crane, undated (Box 71, Object ID: 175.2.0047)
  - Small ceramic object, undated (Box 99, Object ID: 175.2.0048)
  - Envelope Labeled Santa Doll, undated (Box 71, Object ID: 175.2.0050)
  - Baby fist pin from Comly's baby shower, undated (Box 99, Object ID:175.2.0051)
  - Martha Wilson NYU badge, undated (Box 70, Object 175.2.0052)
  - Remember the Triangle Fire 1911-2011 lace sash, undated (Box 70, Object 175.2.0053)
  - Teach 4 Amerika pennant, undated (Box 70, Object 175.2.0054)
- Series IX: Bibliographic Material, 1980-2011
  - Adams, Hugh. Imaging Wales, 2003 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Art of Gillian Jagger, The, 2003 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Art Papers, May/June 2008 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Artist's Projects, 1994 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Bala, Iwan. Essays On Contemporary Art in Wales, 2003 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Bidlo, Mike. Erased de Kooning Drawings, 2005 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Blind Montage, August 1992 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Bomb, Fall 2005 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Coagula, March/April 1998 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Colo. Poesia Rapida, 1980 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Contra Punct, May-August 2001 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Creative Time, 1987-1988 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Culture Counts, 2001 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Darkhawk, January 1994 (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - Episodes of the City, 2007 (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - Flynt, Robert. Lifejacket, 1992 (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - Gibson, Ralph. Pharonic Light, June 1995 (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - Graham, Dan. Dan Graham, 2003 (Box 95, Folder 18)
  - Guyotat, Pierre. Prostitution, 2011 (Box 95, Folder 19)
  - Hendricks, Geoffrey. Between Earth & Sky, 2003 (Box 95, Folder 20)
  - Hendricks, Geoffrey. Four Hands Examining The Color of a Thought, 2003 (Box 95, Folder 21)
  - Hutchins, Alice. Magnetic Encounters, December 2005-January 2006 (Box 95, Folder 22)
  - International Contemporary Art, November 1997-January 1998 (Box 95, Folder 23)
  - International Contemporary Art, February-April 1998 (Box 95, Folder 24)
  - Jones, Patricia Spears. Femme du Monde, 2006 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Kazmierczak,Wladyslaw. Wladyslaw Kazmierczak (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Komar, Vitaly. Three-Day Weekend, 2005 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Kushner, Bill. Love Uncut, 1986 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Lindsay, Arturo. Mapping Ports: ..., 2004 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Live Mag! no. 11 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - L'officina di Nathan Lyons, 1999 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Ludwigsburg, Kunstverein. Lauren Ewing, 1994 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - MacKenzie, John Roderick Dempster. A Retrospective, Oct./Nov. 1997 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Malen, Lenore. Images from Dante, 1991 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Mars, Tanya. Pure Hell, 1990 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Min, Yoong Soon. Yong Soon Min, December 1997 - Jan 1998 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Morgan, Robert C. Angel Orensanz, Spring 2005 (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Movement Research, Fall 1995 (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - New Observations, Winter 1999 (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - On the Next Wave, October 1985 (Box 96, Folder 16)
  - Paper Doll Mega-zine, July 1996 (Box 96, Folder 17)
  - Paramour, Spring/Summer 1996 (Box 96, Folder 18)
  - Paramour, Winter/Spring (Box 96, Folder 19)
  - Paramour, Fall 1996 (Box 96, Folder 20)
  - Paramour, Summer/Fall 1996 (Box 96, Folder 21)
  - Ponge, Francis. The Nature of Things, 2011 (Box 96, Folder 22)
  - The Power to Protect, November-December 2006 (Box 96, Folder 23)
  - Public Illumination Magazine, May 1980 (Box 96, Folder 24)
  - Public Illumination Magazine, 1999 (Box 96, Folder 25)
  - Public Illumination Magazine, 2011 (Box 96, Folder 26)
  - Ringgold, Faith. The French Collection, 1992 (Box 96, Folder 27)
  - Rockburne, Dorothea. The Transcendent Light of Geometry, June/July 2005 (Box 96, Folder 28)
  - Russia 2, 2005-12 (Box 96, Folder 29)
  - SBL (Box 96, Folder 30)
  - Sholette, Gregory. Selected Projects 1980-2003, 2005 (Box 96, Folder 31)
  - Swiss Made, 2005 (Box 96, Folder 32)
- Oversize Series II: Correspondence
  - Subseries A: General Correspondence
    - Cook, Scott Hunter, undated (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Gomez, Edward M., 2002 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Hsieh, Tehching (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Knowles, Michael and Marilyn, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Lapointe, Lyne, 1981 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Messner, Ann, 2006 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Montano, Linda and Tehching Hsieh, 1983-1984 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Point d'ironie - Hans-Ulrich Obrist, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - [Redmond], Layne, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - unsigned, 1988 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - unsigned, undated (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Subseries B: Comly Correspondence
    - Multiple, undated (Box 73, Folder 12)
- Oversize Series III: Subject Files
  - Subseries A: Art and Personal Files
    - Oversize from Bulletin Board, 1984-1986 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Tourist Guide to Jamaica, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Business, gigs, 1991 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Censorship [Comm], 1989-1996 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Film as art, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - General Conceptual, 1972, 1975, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Graphoanalysis, 1974-1977 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Martha Wilson Colloquium-Corroborree Gallery, undated (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - MW in California trip October 15-25 1989 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Words + Works AB, 1975-1976 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Words + Works CDEF, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Words + Works GHI, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Words + Works MNOP (1/2), 1975 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Words + Works MNOP (2/2), 1975 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Words + Works VWXYZ, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Subseries A: Clippings by Year
    - The Baltimore News Post, February 20, 1962 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Political Weeklies/Monthlies, 1982-2004 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Afterimage, January 2985 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - El Internacional Restaurant, 1985 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - The Women's Review of Books, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Prognosis, 1991 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - ZuZu, 1992-1993 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Weekly/Monthly Publications, 1992-1998 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Movement Resources, 1996-1997 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - The New York Times 9/12/01, 2001 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Corrections and Clarifications, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - The Journal of Radical Swimming, 2008 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - The New York Times 3/20/2003 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Museum and Gallery Publications, undated (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Artists Organizations, undated (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - National Campaign for Freedom of Expression, undated (Box 74, Folder 16)
- Oversize Series VI: Flyers, Invitations and Programs
  - Oversize Posters and Flyers, undated (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Oversize Posters and Flyers, undated (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Oversize Posters and Flyers, 1989-1991 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Oversize Posters and Flyers, undated (Flat-file-folder 20)